aycc.org.au 2010-11-15

# Australian Youth Climate Coalition » Contact Us » Privacy Policy

[Home](http://www.aycc.org.au/) » Privacy Policy

Privacy matters, and AYCC is totally committed to ensuring that your participation in our important work protects that privacy.

**Why does AYCC collect personal information?**

AYCC collects personal information principally to allow us to send you opportunities to participate in the youth climate movement. You can ask to stop receiving these emails or change your details at any time by using the link at the bottom of each email or by sending an email to: info@youthclimatecoalition.org

In addition, your information may be used to identify your location (eg electorate, state) and provide targeted and relevant opportunities for you to be part of our activities.

We will also collect personal information for security and verification reasons when accepting donations.

**What does AYCC do with the information?**

AYCC will not provide your personal information to any other organisation except where necessary e.g. to verify credit card transactions or as required by law.

When you send a campaign email through the AYCC site, such as to a newspaper or member of Parliament, the email will include your email address and full name. When you sign a petition through the AYCC site, we will publish your name, town and state, but not your email or physical address.

We’ll make all reasonable efforts to store your information safely and securely.

**For more information…**

If you would like more information on privacy at AYCC, contact us at the office on (02) 9252 5200 or email info@youthclimatecoalition.org.
